I'm just saying that I think it's a good idea.
Yes, sir.
This time
I, Mirei Hoshina and
Cocona
The seven of us would like to go to Osuri-nuri.
Please.
Hey, hey...
I know there's some lag.
Can you hear me?
We can hear you.
We're also streaming on different devices, looking at different showrooms, so...
So, please, give us lots of comments.
Oh, I can hear you.
That's great.
Now, I know we probably won't see each other again, but let's all join in on the title call.
Here we go.
Let's go!
I'm with you.
Here we go.
Showroom
Today is the 43rd Bicchu no YUICIDE SUMUNNA SHOWROOM!
Thank you for visiting our showroom.
This is Uka's showroom, the sister show of our showroom.
So let's take a look at the ranking of the showrooms.
So let's take a look at the ranking.
In fifth place, Shumai, thank you.
In fourth place, Po-chan, thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Monta.
Thank you, J-kun.
First place goes to Tamamin. Thank you.
Thank you very much
Okay, so...
The original avatars in the showroom.
There are many of you here today.
This is the avatar wearing a shrimp.
You can get it for free or for a fee.
You can get it for free when you sign up.
If you haven't done so yet, please get it.
Please try to answer the questions correctly.
I'm sure it's a big hit, but I'd like to introduce you to some of our other characters today.
Niki Bus is so cute. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
If you click on the Twitter icon at the bottom of the screen.
If you click on the Twitter icon at the bottom of the screen, you can promote this show.
Please spread the word on Twitter.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
You're on Twitter.
Some of you have Twitter marks.
Thank you very much.
Please put it on.
Please do.
The manager...
She did this for me.
I'll upload the event as well.
So...
I'd like to go to the corner as soon as possible.
Today is
The 1st Annual World of Suzuruna Album Talk Yay!
Yay! We are Shirito-Ebishi Chugakko!
On March 23rd, we released our new album "Shirito-Ebishi Chugakko"!
Yes, yes!
Yes, I'd like to talk about it a lot today.
First of all, thank you very much for getting it.
Thank you very much.
I've been listening to it a lot.
I heard. I bought the standard edition of AB.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I've got them all on me, so I'd like to introduce them one by one.
First of all, OK!
Server System Limited Edition A.
This is the
This is a very large album of the Elpinsize version.
What's off this one?
First of all, the album, of course.
But also, there was a big live concert at the end of last year called "University Arts Department 2021 Reboot".
There was a big live concert at the end of last year
There's a poster and a trading card for the event.
And there's also a video of the live performance.
This is the A version, and the B version is the LP size version.
And B version is also LP size version.
This one contains the album and 2/2 of the new "Everyting Point".
The B version is the LP size version, which contains the album and our documentary.
And we also designed a poster for each of them.
We designed a poster for each of them.
And there's nine different posters in the box.
And one of ten plus-trading cards.
This is also different from A.
This one is also different from A and is more voluminous.
Both are hard to throw away.
You'll want both!You'll want both!
And here's the regular version
It's the standard CD version.
And this one... can carry letters.
This one is bigger.
You'll be able to keep this in your car and wear it anytime you want.
That's great. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
You said you wanted another one
Excellent. Thank you very much.
I wonder which song she likes best.
I wonder.
What song do you like?
All of them. Oh, I like "Good-bye, Secret Base.
Hmmm...
I can't choose one, Curen.
I like Shooting Stars
I like Kurun.
Why don't you pick a different one?
I'm an hourglass male.
Oh, there's so many.
That's great. That's great.
Okay, bye.
Okay, well...
I'm going to explain the album one song at a time, focusing on one person at a time.
First of all, we have 10 songs each, number 4 is...
A and B, right?
THE FIRST TAKE's seven colors and jumps are on the wind.
So, for now, let's start with these 10 songs.
I'll explain about the 10 songs on the album one by one.
First of all
I'd like to start with the first song, Anytime Anywhere.
Please introduce them.
Yes, Anytime Anywhere.
I don't know, I really love it.
I listen to it a lot in the morning.
I don't know, the way our hands touch each other.
In a world where you can't do that kind of thing nowadays
In a world where you can't do that kind of thing
When I listen to this kind of music
I also feel that, I don't know...
I don't have that corona.
I'd like to go back to that kind of place
I'd like to go back to that kind of thing.
He's touching his hands so much.
I think she has that kind of cheerful personality.
Isn't Rollo's hair really cute?
It's so cute.
My sister did it.
You did it yourself?
So cute!
I know this is a little off topic, but I...
She's adorable.
Eneiny said you were listening to me the morning before.
Oh, yeah.
It's good.
It's refreshing, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
It's true.
It's a good song to listen to in the morning to make your day better. We've also been working on this Anytime Anywhere song.
was pre-released first.
Yes, sir.
January?
Well, it was pre-released on Sovsk.
We liked it so much we listened to it a lot.
You were listening to it, right?
Yes, we were listening to it.
We put Wires in with everyone else.
We were listening to Wires.
We loved it. Before college?
In December?
That's right.
Yes, yes.
That's great. Thank you. Is that the manager?
Thank you very much.
You're all so kind.
Since this is such a happy song, let's continue with the second song.
YELLOW LIGHT.
I would like to explain this one.
This song was written by Tamurapan, who is well known as an Ebitu Slipper,
Tamurapan wrote the first song for us when we were still 6 members in Ebitu,
Aya was still absent at that time, so the five of us performed it together,
At that time, Aya was still absent and the five of us performed the song,
Should the EBITCHU of that time still move forward?
I don't know if I had the courage to move forward yet, or not,
It was a time when I wanted to, but couldn't. It was also a time when I was not sure if I had the courage to go forward,
It was a time when we couldn't find the courage to move forward,
This song is a message from the fans who have been watching us for a long time.
I received such a message from the fans who have been watching us for a long time,
The live video from that time and the lyrics included in the video,
And the lyrics included in the live video.
Ayaka handwrote the lyrics, and we uploaded them to YouTube as a six-member group,
Then three of us joined the group, and we decided to record the song with 10 members at Yellow Light,Then the three of us were added to the group, and the 10 of us decided to record the song with Yellow Light,
The three of us knew the history of Ebichu very well, and we all sang this song with great care,
The first time you sang it, you sang it in the middle notes, right? That's right.
That's right. We sang it for the first time at a medium pitch. That was the first time I sang it,
It was also sung at a college arts and crafts show, etc. It is a wonderful song with six members, but with the addition of the three members, it has become more red and yellow and dite.
I think it is a very nice and joyful song, and I would like to sing it with care.
I want to sing it with care.
Yellow Light is a song that really resonates with me right now.
I'm glad to hear that you were sucked in by Yellow Light.
I'm so happy.
Some of you have received the song.
Thank you very much.
The live performance and the soundtrack are very different.
We re-recorded Yellow Light.
I mean, we only recorded it as a demo.
The six of us...
And we finally recorded it properly for this album, so it might be a little bit different.
Thank you very much.
Then, I would like to go on to the next song, "Kurun".
Please tell us what you love about Kurun.
Yes, I'm going to give an explanation as I love Kurun,
I have really loved this song since I got it.
I felt like I found a song that I really like.
But it's a little bit more k-pop than this.
If Ebitu won this song, it would be a very good song for Ebitu.
I thought it would be a great song for Ebichu.
And when I heard the finished song
I loved it even more than I had imagined.
What is it about this kiln?
It's an image of the night.
I thought I'd like to listen to it in a stylish bar or something.
But...
I don't have the choreography for the dance moves yet, but I'm wondering what kind of fashionable image you have in mind when the dance moves come in.
I'm really looking forward to the live performance.
And, I'm really looking forward to the live performance, and if you haven't heard this song yet, please give it a listen.
Nakata Kyun is pretty good.
NakadaKyun has been working on the album since June? June last year? That was before.
But at that time, the three of us had changed a lot since we recorded this song.
I'm looking forward to seeing them live.
You know, it was so fast.
It's not a bar. Who's a bar?
Happy ending.
Location, location, location.
This was a very difficult song for the three members of Hi-Lit-People, wasn't it?
It was difficult... to be honest, I like it... but it was really difficult to sing.
But I'm sure it's going to be different, and that's the highlight of the live performance.
Okay, we'll go on to "Happy End" and then we'll do "Happy End".
Okay, I'll take this one.
I'll go first.
I'll take this one.
This is a song written by Shinya Ishihara of Sarasin Dock.
This one was also released about a week before the album came out.
And the music video was released a week before the album came out.
The fans really love this song and it's a great song.
It's a song that reminds me of the stage of my first love.
It reminds me of my first love on stage.
It reminds me of my first love.
It makes me sad, but at the same time
I think it's the kind of song that makes you feel warm and close to your old memories
I think it's the kind of song that can make you feel warm.
I think that this song is sung by our
I think this song is sung by the generation of Anemen
I'm sure that the three of us will understand the song differently
I'm sure that the three of us will
I'm sure the three of us will continue to sing the song over the years.
I am sure that the three of us will continue to sing the song in various ways over the years, and the expression of the song will also change.
It's a great song.
It's a very gappa-like song. It warms my heart. Thank you very much.
The choreography is really good too.
It's cute.
Cute.
It's catchy.
Yes, it is. There are a lot of hand gestures that you can do with your hands...
I can do it. There are a lot of hand gestures.
I think it would be great if we could all do it together.
I'd love it if you could film it on TikTok or something.
The choreography is a little difficult.
I've heard recently that the choreography is a bit difficult.
It's very important to get a good video of it.
That's for sure.
Even when you're excited...
What? What do you mean? I'm like, "What?
Yes, I am.
Like this.
I'm sure.
Can we not do this?
Yes, you do.
He said he worked really hard on it.
Wow.
That's great. Thank you very much. Dance with me, please.
I'm so glad you tried it.
Thank you very much.
We're going to make a video explaining it all, so please wait for it.
It's really good. I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you very much.
Next, Tokimekiteki Tetsudo Riron, with lyrics by Ameko Kodama.
This is for Coconner, please.This one goes to Coconner, please.
I thought this song would look great in a live performance.
I think there will be a lot of families who like this song.
Just by listening to it, it really brightens me up.
It really takes me to another world.
It makes me feel like this is a hot live performance.
It's really bright and cheerful.
It's like, "This is EBITCHU, this is EBITCHU.
I think this song is a part of that.
I really love this song!
I know, I love it so much!
If it's an ameko song by ameko, it's true!
It's like candy-coated.
It's so clay!
I'd like to see him go from Omeka Speaver to Crush Weekend Theory, in my opinion.
That's for sure.
I don't know...
I'm looking forward to the choreography for this one too.
looking forward to it
I'm really curious about Clay.
Clay.
Isn't his side tongue amazing?
Oh, my God!
I wish I could have done it.
I wish I could.
I couldn't do it, so I didn't get it.
I don't know, Kaho said he couldn't do it either.
But I guess they didn't pick people who can't speak like that for the roll part.
When they first asked me, "Can you do the roll part? When I was taking it.
They asked me, they asked me.
Well, this way, Ameko-san, Ren-chan, and Ren-kyoku-chan, please look forward to it!
Please look forward to this one, too, at the live performance.
I'm sure it's going to be a lot of fun. I love this one so much.
Okay, on to the next one.
Oh, some people say it's a set up to Mayama's Dragon.
I totally understand
I totally get it
Go on, then
All right
Sugar Glaze, this is Momoka, please.
Yes, Sugar Glaze is really a new opportunity for me.
It's really like an opportunity that we've never had before.
and then they'll fix it afterwards.
Yes, that's right.
Like changing the sound or something.
When we were recording, we had no idea how it was going to turn out.
But when we listened to it
I see.
I'm singing the first part of the song.
That's right.
It's a long part, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
The rhythm and pitch are really great there.
I was so surprised and happy to sing that I didn't expect it to be me.
It's a new song that I've never sung before, with rap parts.
The interlude is also quite long without singing, so I'm looking forward to seeing how the dancing will be at the live performance.
There really hasn't been an autotune song like this before!
I've been thinking about it.
But the recording speed was really too fast.
It was fast.
The trainer made it for us.
It really took less than half an hour.
Recording
After that, the trainer and I talked for about 45 minutes.
It was like we were talking during the recording.
It was like we weren't talking at all.
You talk a lot with a lot of people.
I think it's great that you talk so much with so many people.
There's a lot of people here, and we've already finished recording, so...
I know it's already finished, but I've been talking to so many people.
I'm peeking in and wondering if it's over.
Really, really, really...
That's right.
I talk to a lot of people all the time.
I've been talking with Toriena.
We haven't talked about songs at all.
I see.
Yuria-chan's rap is so cool!
Thank you, I think we only shot one rap.
You're really cool!
After one shot, I was like, "Okay, that's enough.
Wow, that was fast!
That's amazing!
We should definitely sing this together.
We'll sing it together.
Yeah.
It's got a great feel to it.
All of these songs are going to be in the show.
It's really the first take, isn't it?
You're right.
Okay, I'll go with that.
The seventh song is "Good-bye, Secret Base.
This is...
Coconner, please explain.
Yes, this song is...
If you listen to it, you'll understand.
It starts off slow.
and then it starts to run really fast.
It's really amazing.It's really amazing.
I see...
Just by listening to the song, you can feel as if you've seen a story, and the epic worldview really makes you feel like you're about to embark on an adventure.
It's a song that makes you feel like you're about to embark on an adventure, and it starts off slowly and ends slowly too.
I think it's really new that the song starts off slowly and ends slowly.
For me, it made me think of
I was thinking of flack dance. When I was listening to the song.
I thought, "Hatomoko dance. I thought it sounded like fun.
Like a little bit excited.
Yes! I think it's a very grand adventure song.
Yes, it is.
It really is a song like a story, isn't it?
Yes!
Bye bye Ino! Kao's "bye bye ino!
Bye-bye!
You asked me to try to imagine the parting of the brothers.
It was difficult!
It's so hard!
I couldn't keep up with it.
When I heard you got the first one...
Something was playing, right?
Go get some.
something.
Oh, wait a minute. I pretty much started memorizing this.
It was really difficult. This one.
But I thought it would be an important song that would accentuate the live performance.
It was difficult to make a 14 year old associate it with brothers who are separated by breath.
It was difficult.
It really was.
Yoon-ho says he really likes it. It's Yoon-ho's favorite song.
Yes, so I would like to continue.
The 8th song, "The Long Star," I would like to give an explanation,
I have received many comments saying that they really liked "The Long Star,
Thank you very much.
I think the development of this album is going to change from "Nagamisei".
I feel like the development of this album is going to change
I have a feeling that the development of this album is going to change
I heard that it's a good ballad song.
Yes, it is.
The lyrics are also very good.
There are some sad parts in the song.
Like this.
It has a more mature atmosphere.
I wonder if we're still going to sing like this even though we're the 9 of us.
I feel like...
I think it was very thoughtful.
The flow of the song is really comfortable to listen to.
I hope it will be one of those songs that everyone will be humming
I hope it will be one of those songs that everyone will hum all the time.
My wife heard "Shooting Stars" and said it sounded like the 90's.
Oh, it does sound a little bit like the present.
It feels very current.
That's for sure.
She said, "You'll be a good rat!
It's very reassuring.
It's pretty much the life I envisioned.
The lyrics are so close to everyone's heart.
This is such a song!
When I heard it for the first time, it brought tears to my eyes. I want to listen to it at night.
It's a little bit different in nuance,
I think it would be great to sing it at night at Famien,
I think it would be great to sing it outdoors at this year's Famien.
I think it would be great to sing in the light.
Emo!
Emo?
Yes, that's what I thought.
I guess it's like this.
It's a song that can be sung in many different ways.
Okay, let's continue.
The universe is an hourglass.
Okay, this one, Cocona, please.
Yes.
Space is an hourglass. When I listened to this one, I really liked the glassy solo and the way the words were expressed, and I decided when I was recording the song that I would sing with each and every one of these expressions in mind. I tried my best to sing softly and gently with emotion.
I tried my best. This is the other main song of the album, isn't it?
Yes, I like this song.
Yes, I understand. I, uh, like it, too,
Second favorite.
Yes, second favorite.
So this is really my favorite song, too, and I really like the sound and everything,
I can't wait to sing it live.
What do you like about this song, Nanaka?
I don't know, it just draws me in.
It's like a song that didn't seem to exist before.
It was the first time I heard a song like this.
I was really drawn in.
The more I listened to it, the more I liked it.
It's really deep, really deep.
Like the bottom of the ocean
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
That's why I like it.
It's kind of grand, isn't it?
It's like it envelops you.
It's right here on the album.
Right here, right here.
This is definitely the right place for the order of the songs.
I'm sure.
It's like this song, isn't it?
And the last one isThe last from the
The 10th song, which was an earphone live.
Can you please explain what this is?
Yes, please.
This is the first song since we became 9 members, and it's really bright, and the flow from "Hourglass in Space" is really something, because it goes from a grand feeling to a bright song at once, and it's really amazing.
I don't know what's so great about it, like the way they make it sound like an explosion or something, but it's like this song, "Corona"...
It's a really bright song that makes you feel like you're going to show yourself even in a world where you can't really show yourself, like Corona.
It's a song that cheers you up, isn't it?
That's right.
This is the first recording since I became K-Ning.
Was there anything memorable about this recording?
I don't know.
I was asked to sing one time to check the pitch.
I was asked to try singing once to check the pitch, and I suddenly started singing from the first "dah-di-dah-dah-dah".
The truth is, I usually start singing from the lyrics of "Majikon nai wa nada" (I don't want to sing because I'm a magician), but
But I started singing from the introduction, not the interlude, so they said I started singing.
They thought, "Oh, that's right.
I don't know much about it, so I just sing it there.
That's what I do.
What's your first recording here?
The first recording was this air-horror sound, right?
What was the first time? The air-horror sound, right?
The first time was in the FAMILY P.
Oh, yeah.
It was the first time I cried.
I had no idea.
First of all, I didn't know how to open my throat or anything like that, I just put my mouth in front of my mouth, I don't know, and sang.
It didn't go well at all, but I was really feeling cheerful and happy singing.
At the beginning, it's something you can only do at the beginning.
You were crying, because you were on the elevating point.
What is it? Is something coming?
Oh, yeah.
YouTube?
YouTube. YouTube.
Like Famire's Way.
Yeah, the way of the familiars.
It's so hard.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm going to start filming about 10 times
I'm going to introduce the album like this
It's my first time to work on an album
This is the first time I've been involved in it.
I don't know...
I enjoyed this part or struggled with this part. It's not often that you learn a song like this, is it?
Yes, that's right.
When you had to learn one song at a time, you had to learn a song every two days or something.
Was it difficult?
Yes, the songs came in.
You would get a song, record it, and then the next day a new song would come in and you'd have to go over it all over again.
It was really hard work, but it was a milestone for the 10th anniversary of the band, so we did our best.
I worked really hard because it was a milestone album and I had to do my best.
I know... I don't know how you guys manage to make it without breaking your throats, don't you?
Right! We worked hard on the humidification.
Right, you know, there were paper stones around here, right?
It was so dry!
Yuno and I wrung out wet towels and hung them in the room.
We used to sleep with it as a humidifier.
He told me to put a humidifier in the room with the paper mache.
That's true.
I'm begging you.
But the letters... impossible!
I'm very happy that the album was completed without any problems, and I've received many wonderful comments,
Lastly, the first AB version of the album has 7 colors, From the First Take,
The 12th song is Jump! From the First Take, C.T.B.C.O.W.I.Z.Z.I.S.H.Z.HUEY,
And these two songs are included,
This is really another...
It was a really big topic for us between the release of the last album and the release of this album,
We all put a lot of effort into it, and there are some very memorable bursts of takes on this album,
I hope that everyone will be able to hear the tension as well as the commemoration of this first time.
So, this is an album of 10 and 12 songs,
I have worked with many talented producers to create this album, and I hope you will enjoy it.
There are various genres, so if you haven't listened to it yet
If you haven't listened to it yet, please pick it up and listen to it.
If you haven't heard it yet, please pick it up and give it a listen.
We hope you enjoy it!
Please, please, please, please.
I'm so happy to be ranked 3rd in the daily ranking!
So thank you very much everyone!
Now, I'd like to continue with this project.
The title of this project is "Fun and fluffy music at home"!
Yay!
Yes, this is...
Oh, Coconner is gone.
Coconner is gone.
Coconner.
This is a fun project at the remote.
We play a song by Evitune and everyone gets into the groove.
Today, I'd like to choose a song from the album.
Yes, please.
It's on the screen.
You mentioned earlier that you want everyone to dance on TikTok, so I'll choose "Happy End" and "Then and There.
So I'd like to play "Happy End" and "Then and There.
I'd like to play music at home with everyone!
So, that's what I'm going to do,
Kiri Baby Junior High School Happy Ending and Then Some!
Please subscribe to our channel.
Subscribe to our channel
Subscribe to our channelPlease subscribe to our channel.
How was everyone?
Oh, did you dance with us?
Did you dance with us?
I don't know.
I danced while reading the comments.
Was it the first time to see the full dance?
Oh, I didn't go all the way.
But you're right, we haven't shown it on TV yet.
TV and all that.
Is it just for today here?
Rare rare
Rare! Rare!
Oh, everyone brought showers!
Boca is here today.
What do you mean, today?
You don't have a shower today, do you?
No.
No shower.
We danced a little, but I think we danced harder today.
That's for sure.
I hope you're all looking forward to the show.
Thank you very much.
Well, the time has flown by.
Thank you for the 3,000 people who came.
Thank you very much.
Today we mainly talked about the album.
Did you know the songs of the album?
Thank you very much!
Thank you for watching!
Sorry, the manager didn't get the shot.
Yes, okay!
Got it! You got it!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Mr. Sasaki just surprised me.
Okay, that's it.
That's all for us, Sherry and Misuyoka!
Thank you all!
Thank you very much.
I'll go with just a brand in Japan, especially since it's a word I've been envisioning.
I don't want the young people to answer to me.
I don't want to put together a family, interesting roles, genuine gender.
Filtering, scaling, holding, prótouching, deciding on Fujipawa...
Büchels, but I guess you are still doing Action.
I'm sure you've made mistakes in complementing На's brand of Ч thế ipu.
Yes, so thank you to everyone who stayed for the review session!
Thank you very much.
How was it?
How was it? It says, "How was it?
Everyone said it was a rather serious session.
I think I did a good job of conveying the idea of the album.
The song introductions were perfect, and there was no reflection on the show.
It certainly didn't feel like a Tevichu showroom.
That's for sure.
You're always hanging out so much.
I'm looking forward to the tour. I forgot to announce it earlier.
Yes, you did.
7SENSEFUL album series EBITCHE is now on sale!
New Hands Mission Stage Anniversary Tour 2022
It's called 2022 door.
We'll do 14 shows in 12 cities.
Please come, everyone!
Please come!
Come on in.
It's the first tour for both of you.
You must be really excited.
Yes, I'm really looking forward to it.
Is there anything in particular you're looking forward to?
I'm, uh...
Osaka?
Yeah.
Osaka? Osaka? Fukuoka?
In Kyushu?
I've never been to Kyushu. So I'd like to go to Kyushu.
I'd like to go to Kyushu.
I'll go there!
I'm going to eat a lot of good food!
On the 7th?
So I was really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to Hokkaido.
You've never been there?
I've been to Hokkaido, but it's a big place and I've never been there, so I'm really looking forward to it.
Also, Kaho-chan mentioned before that Osaka is getting a little loose, and I've heard that May 5 is a great date for the Osaka leg of the tour.
I heard that they were going to be pissed off.
Ouch!
I will do my best.
I'll do my best.
Osaka really gets angry a lot.
It's really getting a little tense. The music room.
I will do my best not to let that happen this year.
I will try my best not to let that happen this year.This year I will do my best to make sure that does not happen.
I always do it right.
Well, well, anyway, what makes the 5th especially is the 10th anniversary. With the commemoration of the 10th anniversary of the major level.
It's our first anniversary here in the middle, so everyone, please come and visit us as it's a memorable day for you.
We will be going to various places for the first time in a long time, so please take a look at our website and other details,
I hope you will come and visit us at a venue near you.
Rehearsals for the tour will start soon, so I will do my best.
I will do my best!
I will do my best! So that's it.
Yes, I know, the venue in Osaka used to be the venue for Move, but it turned out to be a coronavirus inoculation site.
Oh, that's right! That's right!
I couldn't go, right? That's right!
That's right!
Everyone say good luck, and take care of yourselves. Yes! Thank you!
So, how was it? How was today?
How was it?
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you very much!
Honhin-san's progress was so smooth that I couldn't find the right time to enter...
I couldn't get it...
On the other hand, how was it remotely? I think it was the first time for both of you.
Yes, it was.
Well, I...
Tell us about it.
I'm so sorry that I kind of jumped away for a moment.
It suddenly disappeared, didn't it?
I don't know why it disappeared, but I don't know what happened, so I'm sorry.
I don't know why it disappeared, but I don't understand it myself, so I'm sorry,
That's where the "pudding" was born.
That's right.
I guess everyone had a good radio wave.
About one person.
Most of them froze up about three times.
I think I finally lost my face.
Oh, I see.
There was a time, wasn't there?
Yes, there was. It was like a specialty.
A specialty.
It was kind of fun, and I was often invited to do remotes.
Maybe after a lot of remotes, I'd go back to the studio,
I think it's a hundred times easier to do it in the studio.
I think it is 100 times easier to do it in the studio, so I hope this was a good experience for you, and maybe next time we can do it in the studio again.
Also, there were a lot of comments that someone came into Mr. Honhin's room, and it was like that person was reflecting on the situation.
That's Mr. Takagi, isn't it? We will be broadcasting Momokuro-chan from 9:00 p.m., so if you enjoyed it, please watch it.
I was really surprised. People were delivering and saying "kon-kon-kon-kon" and so on.
It's understandable, though.
The next time is still undecided, so we will let you know as soon as it is decided.
We will let you know as soon as it is decided.
So, thank you all for watching, and we'll see you soon.
We will do our best to take care of our health, and we will do our best to get everyone humidified together soon.
We will do our best to take care of our health, and we hope you will join us in making the album more exciting.
The hashtag for the album is hashtag Ebichu Seventh.
Please join us in the excitement of the album!
Well then, thank you so much for today, see you next time, bye-bye!
Bye bye bye thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Questions and comments